yardit.com 2010-01-13

# Yardit.com - Privacy Policy

At Yardit, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Yardit, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as Comcast or ATT), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on YarditYardit to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Editing or Deleting Your Account Information**  
You may request deletion of your user account by [contacting us](mailto:admin@yardit.com). Content or other data that you may have provided to us and that is not contained within your user account, such as posts that may appear within our forums, may continue to remain on our site at our discretion even though your user account is deleted. Please see our [Terms of Use](http://www.yardit.com/terms.php) for more information.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.

**Children**  
We do not allow persons who are ages seventeen or younger to become members of this site.

**NO GUARANTEES.**  
While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.

AVOID SCAMS AND FRAUD: When posting free classified ads, beware or any deal involving Western Union, Moneygram, wire transfer, cashier check, money order, shipping, escrow, any promise of transaction protection/certification/guarantee, or your personal or banking information. When it comes to free classified ads, safety comes first."
